(Howard:)She's right.
So your boyfriends a fixer-upper.
Most of them are.
(Bernadette:)I mean, look at this guy.
You think he came like this?
(Bernadette:)When I met him,
he was a hot, goofy mess.
(Bernadette:)Now, he's been to space.
(Bernadette:)That's all me.
-l had a little to do with it.
-Oh, sure you did.
(Bernadette:)Who's Mama's big space man?
(Howard:)I am.
(Leonard:)They've been in there,
like, half an hour.
(Penny:)Yeah, for future reference,
that's a while.
(Leonard:)-How long should we stay?
-I don't know. I'm kind of hungry.
(Leonard:)-I saw a Thai place next door.
-OK.
(Leonard:)-How's she doing?
-How is everything?
(Raj:)She's gonna be OK.
They're gonna let me take her home.
(Sheldon:)Good.
(Vet:)So I want you to keep
a close eye on her
(Vet:)for the next 24 hours.